<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Culture on elliott.io</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/culture/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Culture on elliott.io</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/culture/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Designing a Culture of Innovation</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/pitch-fest/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/pitch-fest/</guid>
      <description>⊕ Themes: Process and Planning, Strategy, Technology, Entrepreneurship Goals: Our team was tasked with developing a venture pipeline of fintech businesses to be grown as arms of the more established company. We were tasked with everything from identifying ideas that had merit, creating plans to build technology, and developing revenue models and go to market strategies. An Innovation Hub Trying to Find its Footing TNB, The National Bank, had made huge strides in technology while also keeping their core products moving forward at a conservative pace.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Designing for Collective Accountability</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2r/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2r/</guid>
      <description>There is one situation that all designers, at least this designer, loves and fears at the same time–working for another designer.&#xA;⊕ Themes: Internal Service Design, Operations, Project Management, Process and Collaboration Scoping The assignment was to develop a template for design projects. The client was a design firm of 35 people, and would have small teams of 2 to 5 people work projects, but there was no consistent process moving from business lead to contract through completion.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
