<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Points on elliott.io</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/points/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Points on elliott.io</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/points/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Design is Strategy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/design-is-strategy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/design-is-strategy/</guid>
      <description> design …the art or action of conceiving of and producing such a plan or drawing… purpose, planning, or intention that exists or is thought to exist behind an action, fact, or material object… strategy a plan of action or policy designed to achieve a major or overall aim… </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Designers are the Unreasonable Men</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/designers-are-the-unreasonable-men/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/designers-are-the-unreasonable-men/</guid>
      <description>&amp;#34;The reasonable man adapts himself to the world; the unreasonable one persists in trying to adapt the world to himself. Therefore all progress depends on the unreasonable man.&amp;#34;&#xA;George Bernard Shaw via Tony Golsby-Smith</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Dumb are Mostly Intrigued by the Drum</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-dumb-are-mostly-intrigued-by-the-drum/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-dumb-are-mostly-intrigued-by-the-drum/</guid>
      <description>As a Designer, I make plenty of presentations, and having made plenty of presentations, I&amp;#39;ve gotten pretty good at making convincing presentations. You can tell when your watching a presentation made by a designer. You&amp;#39;ve got a lot of white space in documents, and huge full bleed images of &amp;#34;the user.&amp;#34;&#xA;Big pictures, impactful emotional quotes, videos, are all great tools at conveying a message, but when do we move from making an argument and showing an audience about a current set of people to pulling on their heart strings and taking advantage of our human nature?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Generalist&#39;s Job is to Have Many Known Unknowns</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/generalists-job-is-to-have-many-known-unknowns/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/generalists-job-is-to-have-many-known-unknowns/</guid>
      <description>The Unknown&#xA;As we know, There are known knowns. There are things we know we know. We also know There are known unknowns. That is to say We know there are some things We do not know. But there are also unknown unknowns, The ones we don&amp;#39;t know We don&amp;#39;t know. –Donald Rumsfeld&#xA;I&amp;#39;ve been spending a great deal of time thinking of what makes designers, liberal artists, generalists, different.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
