<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>B2B on elliott.io</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/b2b/</link>
    <description>Recent content in B2B on elliott.io</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/b2b/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A BI Tool for Self-Insured Co&#39;s</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/innovu/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/innovu/</guid>
      <description>Understanding User Workflows in Complex B2B Software Overview ⊕ Themes: Human Computer Interaction, User Research A few designers were hired by a 100 person company. The company was engineering/data driven, and now started to see the cracks in having a UI that was built for internal users that was a 1:1 representation of the underlying data model. The two designers were the first designers to take a look at the UI since the conception of the product.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LegalSifter: From Consumer App to B2B</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/legalsifter/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/legalsifter/</guid>
      <description>+&#xA;After running a design firm for less than a year, there were several occasions when a project would come in and it didn’t make sense to hire a lawyer. We’d sign contracts with no legal review thinking we’d save a few thousand dollars. But buried deep in a multi-page dense contract, there would be an innocuous phrase.&#xA;⊕ “payable no later than net 30 days to Consultant, upon the completion &amp;hellip; and subject to test and acceptance” The phrase didn’t raise any red flags in my head, but 6 months after the project finished, the final deliverables were waiting for acceptance.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
