<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Marketplace on elliott.io</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/marketplace/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Marketplace on elliott.io</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/marketplace/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Designing an App with Friends</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/likenow/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/likenow/</guid>
      <description>One conversation turned into a company&#xA;LikeNow started from a single conversation. Joey had the realization that startup &amp;#34;dogfooding&amp;#34; culture had left out lower-income citizens from the majority of startup ideas. I was working on an on-demand company to buy back used electronics with a demographic mainly in lower-income areas. After that conversation, Joey and I decided to join forces, both expanding the concept from just buying back used electronics, to covering the entire spectrum of the Craigslist Economy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finding Innovation in SBA Loans</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/offset/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/offset/</guid>
      <description>The bank sent me to investigate potential financial opportunities related to Small Business Loans. I was chosen to lead a team since the bank was interested in innovative products that could spin out of the bank and not efficiency plays. I took along a business lead to help with the financial analysis and industry expertise.&#xA;Understanding the Lifecycle of an SBA Loan I interviewed dozens of stakeholders and for each discrete step I outlined who was involved (circles) and what actions were taken (boxes), starting from the beginning of the process when an SMB was looking for a loan:</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
